撃て
Fire!
二班　撃て
Unit Two...
fire!
よし　総員　第四波に備えろ
南西方面では　すでに敵機の侵入を許している
ここが突破されれば　新宿は終わりだ
Very good.
All units, stand by for the fourth wave!
なんとしてでも食い止めろ
帝鬼軍をなめるなよ　吸血鬼ども
The southwest has already fallen to enemy aircraft!
Should our ranks crumble here, Shinjuku will be done for!
Do everything in your power to stop them!
Don't make light of the Demon Army, vampire scum!
行くよー
Here comes the airplane!
なかなかうまいだろ　ピンポイントだ
自慢できるほどじゃないな
右に3メートルずれてたぞ
相変わらず細かいな
Damn, I'm good.
Bullseye!
This is hardly worth bragging about.
You were off by ten feet to the right.
Don't sweat the small stuff, man.
I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you, I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame
We were all swept away
I'll come and get you; I am always ready to fight
Don't take all of the weight
You always do
There will always be something you cannot control
So don't take all of the blame
We will overcome. Your salvation has begun
We were all swept away
Don't take all of the weight
You always do
No signs, no lights
There will always be something you cannot control
Such a mess all over
We will overcome
Don't kill your hopes
Your salvation has begun
You make me realize who I need
No signs, no lights
Such a mess all over
I'll be there, hold on
Don't kill your hopes
They'll change you somehow
You make me realize who I need
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
I'll be there, hold on
The shadows appear
Illusions are born
They'll change you somehow
So where are you now?
The fallen angels you run with don't know
I'll reach you by dawn
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
The shadows appear
Illusions are born
Torn old sepia photographs show
The fallen angels you run with don't know
Our fragile preious world
Must discard it, respond to the call
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Torn old sepia photographs show
本字幕由诸神字幕组出品，仅供学习交流，禁止用于商业用途
更多中日双语字幕，尽在 i.kamigami.org 和微博 @诸神字幕组
日听:鱼子酱&paper   翻译:小悠&小江   校对:夜神&Lucifer   时间轴:阿水   压制:久嘉
Our fragile precious world
Must discard it, respond to the call
Vampire
Onslaught
急げ
Hurry!
奴らは
Where are they?!
West!
西だ
Shinjuku is the Japanese Imperial
Demon Army's second-largest foothold!
新宿は日本帝鬼軍の第二都市だぞ
The city is currently under vampire fire.
吸血鬼の侵入を許すなんて
How could we allow the vampires to breach it?!
All civilians should quickly evacuate to the east defensive barrier.
What are those damn extermination units doing?!
吸血鬼殲滅部隊は何してんだ
The city is currently under vampire fire.
どうなってる
What's going on?
Can't you hear?
言葉通りでしょ　吸血鬼たちは攻めてきて…
The vampires are attacking—
クソ　完全に戦争じゃねぇか
Shit, it's all-out war down here!
グレン中佐が言ってた通りだ
It's just as Lieutenant Colonel Guren said.
関西の吸血鬼どもは　日本帝鬼軍を潰すつもりだ
The vampires from the Kansai region are planning to destroy the Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
やれ
Fire!
Are those Infernal Arms like mine?
あれって僕と同じ鬼呪装備
A much weaker version, yes.
のダウングレード版です
鬼呪装備を簡略化した　通称呪術装備だ
Those are called Runic Arms.
They're simplified Infernal Arms, more or less.
Hey!
来い
This way!
All men, arms at the ready!
総員　戦闘準備
Sir!
はっ
私たちも出るぞ
We're moving out!
Yoichi, shoot the chopper down!
与一　お前はヘリだ
Got it!
こっちも終わったぞ
We're done here!
よくやってくれた　礼を言う
You guys were a huge help.
I appreciate it.
私は新宿警備部隊　第三小隊所属　長井伍長だ
Corporal Nagai of the Shinjuku Security Unit,
Third Platoon, at your service.
君たちは吸血鬼殲滅部隊だな
You are the vampire extermination unit, correct?
月鬼ノ組です
We're from the Moon Demon Company.
月鬼ノ組か　まだ付きが残ってるな
The Moon Demon Company?
Seems like there's still hope yet.
お前ら　すぐに手配してくれ
Fire her up, boys.
Sir!
はっ
先程　西防御壁が突破され　吸血鬼侵入を許した
I've just received word that the vampires
have broken though the west defensive barrier.
現在は迎撃部隊が食い止めているが
The counter-attack squad is currently barring them from further entry, but they won't last long.
長くは持たん
Our tactical situation is worse than I thought.
思った以上に　戦況が悪いようですね
Yes, it's like something out of a nightmare.
まるで悪夢だよ
I need you guys to head west
and fend off the vampire onslaught.
君たちには急ぎ西へ向かい　吸血鬼討伐に加わって欲しい
言われるまでもねぇよ
You don't need to ask.
それが任務だからなぁ
That's what we're here for, after all.
Good to hear.
頼もしいな
長井伍長　準備完了しています
Corporal Nagai!
Preparations have been completed.
Right.
うん　俺は彼らを防衛地点までお連れする
I'll be taking them to the defense line.
ここは任せたぞ
Hold the fort for me.
Sir!
はっ
さ　乗ってくれ
All right, everyone hop in.
Well, well. So it's begun.
始まったなぁ　本当に攻めてきやがった
They're seriously coming at us.
Let's see... The commander should be nearby.
んで　どーこが司令塔だ
おーっと　やべぇ
Whoa there. He can sense me from this far away?
この距離で気付くのかよ
あの　グレン中佐
Um, Lieutenant Colonel Guren?
Now's not really the time to be making idle observations.
こんなところで悠長にしてる場合では…
Well, it's not like I'm sitting here for fun or anything.
別に悠長にしてるわけじゃねぇけどな
防衛線には見張り塔がいるだろう
We need to post lookouts for our defense, right?
とすれば　吸血鬼どもはここも狙ってくると思っ…
I figured the vampires would target here as—
Ah, right on cue.
言ってるそばから来たぞ　小百合
Sayuri!
What?
遅ぇよ　美十
Fashionably late, aren't you, Mito?
Late, you say?
何が遅いよ　急にこんなところに呼び出して
Hardly the attitude I'd expect from someone who summoned me on such short notice.
どういうことですか
We've returned, Lieutenant Colonel Guren.
グレン様　ただいま参りました
なーんかすげぇこと始まったみたいだなぁ
Sounds like there's something big going on.
What's the plan?
どうすんだ
新宿の殲滅部隊はまるで対応できてないぞ　これ
The extermination unit sure
doesn't seem to be holding up.
よし　全員揃ったな
All right, looks like we're all here.
Shigure, how are Yuu and friends doing?
時雨　優のチームはどうだ
無事民間人の解放を終え　新宿に入りました
They've successfully rescued the civilians and have entered Shinjuku.
Oh? That was fast.
早いな　じゃあこの戦争にも参加できるなぁ
They're ready for this war, then.
強くなるには実践が一番だ　死ななきゃ強くなる
On the battlefield, what doesn't kill you
makes you stronger.
よし　行くぞお前ら
All right.
We're heading out, guys.
司令塔は五丁目の交差点だ
The commander's at the fifth district's
main intersection.
頭を潰しゃ　状況も変わんだろ
Lop his damn head off,
and we just might see some progress.
Someone's taken an interest in us.
これは見られてますね
見られてる
Interest?
It's nothing. I'm just rambling to myself.
いえいえ　こちらの話です
How are you finding Tokyo?
それよりどうです　久しぶりの東京は
It's been a while, no?
いい思い出はないかもしれませんが
You may have some rather
unpleasant memories about the place,
実際に帰ってくると　考え深いものがあるんじゃないですか
but doesn't being here in person
just touch your heart?
おまけに百夜の優ちゃんに会えるとなると　なおさら
Especially since you have the chance to see your beloved Hyakuya Yuu.
Aren't you parched, Mika?
君は血を吸わなくていいんですか　ミカ君
It'd be best to drink now, on the battlefield,
戦時中の今飲まないと
僕らの街では　直接人間の血を飲めませんよ
since our city forbids
directly feeding on humans within its limits.
お前は法を守らず　僕の血を飲んでたじゃないか　フェリド・バートリー
That's funny coming from someone
who broke that very law and drank my blood,
Ferid Bathory.
人聞きの悪いこと言わないでくださいよ　ミカ君
Don't say such scandalous things.
You'll damage my reputation, Mika.
君の方から飲んでと言ってきたんでしょう
It was you who came to me and offered your blood,
only to steal my gun and map from my mansion.
で　僕の屋敷から銃や地図を盗んでた　違いましたっけ
Am I wrong?
お前の薄汚い手のひらの上で　踊らされているとも知らずにな
I unwittingly played right into your dirty hands.
Indeed.
僕はお前の道楽で家族を皆殺しにされた
And now my family's dead,
all for your sickening amusement.
Aw, you're still rattling on
about that ancient history, even now?
吸血鬼になった今でも　まだそんな古いことを怒ってるんですかぁ
いや　僕が怒りを感じるのは
No. I'm simply upset at myself for being powerless to protect my family.
家族を守るだけの力がなかった自分にだけだ
相変わらず自罰的ですね
A chivalrous knight as always.
で　最後に残った家族　百夜の優ちゃんだけは守る　ですか
And what of your last family member?
Are you going to defend your precious Hyakuya Yuu's honor?
愛だなぁ
That's love for you.
でもね　ミカ君
Oh, but do keep in mind, Mika.
人間の血は吸っとかなきゃダメですよ
Refusing to drink human blood won't do you any favors.
血が欠乏した吸血鬼がどうなっちゃうか　君も知ってるでしょ
You know what happens to vampires
who don't get proper nutrition, don't you?
Four years earlier
さあ　ミカ　血を吸いなさい
Go on, Mika.
Drink his blood, and your biological growth will come to a halt.
そうすれば　あなたの細胞は動きを止める
Your body will be made immortal,
with strength beyond that of a human.
人間を超越した力と　老いのない肉体
完全な吸血鬼へと変貌する
You will be reborn anew as a vampire.
ぼ…僕は吸血鬼になるつもりはない
Th-There's no way I'm drinking his blood!
そんなこと言っても　体は我慢できないでしょう
Or so you say, but your body is craving it, no?
Your whole body must be in agony,
全身が痛いはず
渇いて渇いて仕方ないはず
your throat searing and parched.
我慢せず　欲望のままに
Don't resist.
Succumb to your desire.
うるさい
Never!
じゃあ　このまま死ぬ
Then will you die?
I'd rather die than turn into a monster!
吸血鬼になるくらいなら　死んだほうがましだ
I see.
そう
True, transcending the limits of old age and wallowing in boredom may not be the greatest use of your time.
まあ　確かに
千年二千年と成長もなく退屈するのは賢い選択じゃないかもしれない
でもあなた　もう普通には死ねないわよ
But death will no longer come to you
as it would a human.
私があなたを変えちゃったから
Because I've changed you.
血を飲まなければ　あなたは意志のない醜い「鬼」に変わってしまう
Without blood, you'll become an empty, withering demon without will.
That's why you must drink—
だから人間の血を
I won't do it!
絶対に嫌だ
I...
僕は…僕はお前らになるつもりはない
I won't become one of your kind!
じゃ　別の選択肢をあげるわ
Well, how about I give you another option?
私の血を飲むのよ
Drink my blood.
Drink it to stay alive.
飲み続けて生き長らえる
我慢する必要なんてどこにもないわ
There's no reason for you to fight it.
Come, now.
さあ　お飲みなさい
い…言ったはずだ
I-I told you!
お前らになるつもりはない
I won't turn into a vampire!
Oh, was the temptation too strong?
そう
飲むの
You won't be able to leave me now.
ならあなたはもう　私から離れられないわね
永遠に　永劫に　あなたは私の犬になるのよ
For all of eternity,
you'll be my dog, Hyakuya Mikaela.
百夜ミカエラ
Ten days worth of Krul's blood.
クルルの血が十日分
十日以内に優ちゃんを見つけないと
Ten days to find Yuu.
あと１５分ほどで防衛地点に到着する　準備を整えておいてくれ
We'll be arriving at the defense line in fifteen minutes.
Please be on standby.
最前線に行く前にちょっといいですか　優さん
Before we grace the front lines, do you have a moment, Yuu?
Yeah? What's up?
なんだよ
This may be rather sudden,
but it's time to kick off your first training lesson!
突然ですが
今から優さんたちの第一回目の修業を始めます
What? Training?
修業？
こんな状況で何言ってんだ
Have you seen what's going on outside?
I'm saying this because of what's outside.
こんな状況だから言ってます
皆さんも吸血鬼の貴族とぶつかって分かったとは思いますが
I'm sure our encounter with that noble has made you aware that even with the Black Demon Series,
いくら「黒鬼」シリーズを保有しているとはいえ
今のままだと瞬殺です
there's still a high chance of you dying
within two seconds flat.
None of you will be of use
on the front lines right now.
前線に出ても　まるで役に立たんな
もうね　あれです
Really, how do I put this...
地面に落ちてるうんち以下の存在
You all might as well be roadkill.
What are you even talking about?
何の話だよ
冗談はあとだ
Save your jokes for later.
What did you have in mind?
で　何すりゃいい
いや　といっても別に今回は特別なことは何もないんですが
Well, it's nothing too fancy, but there's a little something that might give you the edge you need.
Simply put:
やるのは簡単
these.
これです
薬？
Pills?
今一番最先端の修業法だ
It's a state-of-the-art training method.
In other words, performance-enhancing drugs.
まあ　ドーピングですね　ドーピング
飲むと鬼と同化しやすくなって　本来の力が引き出せます
They allow you to synchronize with the demon more easily,
drawing out your true power.
So if I take that, the vampire nobles...
じゃ　それ飲みゃ吸血鬼の貴族も
...won't beat you to a pulp, at least.
少なくとも　すぐに殺されたりはしなくなるでしょう
理論上は一錠飲めば1.5倍
Theoretically, one pill multiplies your strength by 1.5,
and two should multiply it by 1.8.
二錠飲めば1.8倍の力が使えます
Seriously?!
マジかよ　んじゃ十錠くらい飲みゃ
So if I take, like, ten of them...
You'd probably be strong enough to kill a god.
神でも殺せるんじゃないですか
Then let's do this thing—
じゃ　早く
But your organs will come
spilling out with just three pills.
ただ三錠で内蔵が破裂します
What?
Even with two pills, you'll sustain severe trauma and could die of shock.
二錠でもショック死しかねない　深刻なダメージがあります
なので普通は一錠まで
That's why we usually take just the one.
おまけに効果時間は１５分だ
Plus, it only lasts for fifteen minutes.
薬が切れた瞬間　完全な無防備になる
Once the pill wears off, you'll be completely vulnerable.
Here you go.
はい　どうぞ
あの貴族とぶつかった時　なぜこれを渡さなかった
So where were these when we ran into that noble?
あん時これ飲んでりゃー
If we all took these—
We still wouldn't have won.
勝てませんでしたよ
Huh?
It takes ten seconds for the pill to kick in.
薬の効果が出始めるのに10秒掛かります
そして10秒もあれば
And with those ten seconds,
彼は私たちを皆殺しにできた
he could have killed us all.
One more question.
もう一ついいか
これがお前の言ってた　鬼呪装備の本当の使い方なのか
Is this what you meant by taking
full advantage of an Infernal Arm?
If I use this, will I be able to draw out
my weapon's power to its true potential?
これさえ飲めば　今度こそ鬼呪装備の力を全部引き出せる
Not quite. This is only temporary.
いえいえ　これは一時的なものです
鬼呪の力を使いこなすにはもっと勉強と修業が必要ですが
Mastering your weapons requires
copious amounts of study and training,
but we don't have time for that right now,
with war just around the corner and whatnot.
でも今はそれやってる時間ないでしょう
何せ戦争始まっちゃいましたし
True.
確かにな
それが戦場だ
That's life on the battlefield.
お前　そればっかだな
Don't you have any other lines to say?
What? You wanna go?!
ああ　今なんて言った
皆さん　来ますよ
They're on the move!
おっさん
Corporal!
Yuu!
優さん
クソ
Yoichi!
与一
Roger that!
うん
シノア　おい
Shinoa.
Hey.
シノア　おい
Shinoa.
Wake up!
地下鉄のようですね
It appears we've landed in the subway.
Yeah.
ああ
みっちゃんたちは
Where are Mitsu and the guys?
見える範囲にはいねえ
Nowhere to be found.
But right now, we need to do
something about the corporal.
それより　おっさんをなんとかしねえと
地上に出れば臨時拠点があるでしょう
There should be a temporary base
if we go above ground.
そこまで行けば医療を受けれます
He can be treated there.
Hey, dumbass!
おい　馬鹿優
聞こえか
You there?
お前ら　無事か
Are you guys all right?
当たり前だ
Obviously!
こんなとこでくたばるわけねえだろう　馬鹿が
Like hell we'd die in a place like this, shithead.
出れそうか
Can you guys get out?
問題ない
No problem!
Then you go ahead!
じゃ　皆さんは先に行ってください
私たちはちょっと寄り道するんで
We're going to stop by somewhere.
防衛地点で合流するぞ
We'll meet you at the defense line!
Um, but...
でも
遅れんなよ
Don't be late!
najimeta shiro torikago sumi
I used to like the light, my corner of the cage
馴染めた白　鳥がご隅　鼓動獲たツボミも
kodou eta tsubomi mo
I'm a flower bud made flesh
置き去り声　眩めた　記憶の影
okizarigoe kurameta kioku no kage
Blinding memories cry after me
I need your blood
i need your blood
you read love tonaeru
You speak of love to me
You really love 唱える
agaku red light
The red lights dance
足掻くRed Light
嗅ぎ分けた音　音と
kagiwaketa neon to
The neon lamps
こじ開けたReasonが
kojiaketa reason ga
and the madness of the world
ただ平行に並ぶ
tada heikou ni narabu
share a vanishing point
Come on break it down for me!
Come on, break it down for me
come on, break it down for me
A river will flow
a river will flow
KEYがない「欲しい」でも　利害鳴る鈴
My desires remain unfulfilled
key ga nai hoshii demo
rigai naru suzu
A melody of ups and downs
懺悔さえ乾いた　４拍子が　奏でた意図を辿る
zange sae kawaita yonbyoushi ga
Our song follows the sheet of our will,
kanadeta ito wo tadoru
no longer capable of penance
木漏れ日の　赤が　騒ぐ
kanadeta ito wo tadoru
Crimson beams assault my vision
komorebi no aka ga sawagu
次回　終わりのセラフ
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
Choices and
Consequences
"Choices and Consequences."